<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Documentation of Alumni Data Analytics Project for Office Assistants</title><link>/doc-ds-oa/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Documentation of Alumni Data Analytics Project for Office Assistants</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/doc-ds-oa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Process</title><link>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/functions/process/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/functions/process/</guid><description>Process existing/new data # Process, as the name suggests, is processing and cleaning all the data you have. You need to have the data folder residing in the directory in order to proceed.
Two situations # There are two situations leading you to encounter different things:
When you just want to process the old data to see what the result looks like; When you have new grads' information to process Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the easier one: old data.</description></item><item><title>Quickstart</title><link>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/quickstart/</guid><description>Quickstart # Prerequisites # Python 3.9 or higher (I think version &amp;lt; 3.9 should work fine, but I use 3.9, so it&amp;rsquo;s advisable to keep the same Python version to avoid weird problems.) Git Github/Github Desktop Any text editor or IDE. I suggest using Visual Studio Code Python Version # python3 --version If you do not have python installed or the version is incorrect, follow the python official documentation to install/upgrade.</description></item><item><title>Clean</title><link>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/functions/clean/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/functions/clean/</guid><description>Clean cache and trash # Please be aware that &amp;ldquo;Clean&amp;rdquo; here does not refer to data cleaning, but refer to cleaning cache and trash generated during the data processing and cleaning job.
If you run the clean function, your console might look like this:
&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Entering clean cache mode... We have removed unnecessary folders. [ -- See you next time! -- ] You can find console log file in log/Jul-21-2021-158.</description></item><item><title>Exit</title><link>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/functions/exit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/functions/exit/</guid><description>Exit the program # You can simply run the exit function to exit the program.
Please note that exit will still generate console logs inside the log folder.</description></item><item><title/><link>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/code-structure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/processing/code-structure/</guid><description>The code structure # Although the code are well-documented and structured, it is still worth explaining the overall structure for you to familiarize.
code directory # The code directory looks like this:
. ├── clean.py ├── console_controller.py ├── main.py ├── preprocessing.py ├── process.py └── title_merge.py clean.py It will merge job titles based on the algorithm and unify time format to be xx.xx years. console_controller.py It controls all the console output &amp;amp; recording.</description></item><item><title/><link>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/contribute/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/doc-ds-oa/docs/doc/contribute/</guid><description>How to contribute to this documentation # Hugo # This documentation is built on Hugo. Hugo is a really fast static site generator built by Go. You will need prior Hugo and Markdown knowledge to proceed.
Hugo Documentation # The Hugo Documentation is pretty useful for learning hugo. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to know all the details. Just basic hugo commands, file directory, and how to write new pages.</description></item></channel></rss>